{
    "id": "f09f761b4a04494e981f699a515d87ea",
    "title": "Omission Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have met him a few days ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "a",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8c560dee981d4b569f1a41d625da802e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you like some other peas?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "some",
                "other"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b49686d2700949c0b3f6960fe5e3dd35"
        },
        {
            "question": "Janet, who is my best friend, she is on holiday at the moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "she",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "991ebf36566c4651bd37caa26ac4e9fd"
        },
        {
            "question": "The baby resembles to its mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ec7ed508b65743ea98f834245b91ed89"
        },
        {
            "question": "The train had left before we reached to the station.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had",
                "to",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fcaf85ca55e34a68b764ac11ef21f200"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was so big a man such that he could not sit in that chair.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c99879872f244afe9f5a383a08e3807e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why donâ€™t you think more about others people?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "about",
                "others",
                "people"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "6ba0165ff5ca4f7cb1c30f0ede567c66"
        },
        {
            "question": "Perhaps you could correct any of mistakes I have made.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "perhaps",
                "could",
                "any",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "324522c83c8a465193be3236e9ca7f27"
        },
        {
            "question": "The life is quite complicated.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the",
                "quite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4ebdc4fa6b4e493ba05b3943aa8e35d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you got a cheaper sort of a camera?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "got",
                "sort",
                "a"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3f17a2f324154ade8ca19bc77525cb4d"
        }
    ]
}